Guide to the Stephen M. Cabrinety Collection in the History of Microcomputing, ca. 1975-1995
Department of Special Collections
Stephen M. Cabrinety Collection in the History of Microcomputing,
ca. 1975-1995
Special Collections M0997
Cabrinety, Stephen M.
815.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access
Access restricted; this collection is stored off-site in commercial storage from which material is not routinely paged. Access to the collection will remain restricted until such time as the collection can be moved to Stanford-owned facilities. Any exemption from this rule requires the written permission of the Head of Special Collections.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Patricia Cabrinety and Lawrence Cabrinety, 1998 and 1999.
Biography
Stephen Cabrinety (born Aug. 4, 1966) was Director of Development of Superior Software, Inc. He founded the non-profit organization, the Computer History Institute for the Preservation of Software (C.H.I.P.S.) in 1989. His dream was to permanently locate his collection where it could serve as a museum, an educational tool and an archive for scholarly research. He died on Oct. 4, 1995.
Scope and Content
Collection contains software, computer hardware, peripheral devices, hand-held games, and computer industry literature documenting the microcomputing gaming industry during its formative years.
Collection Contents
- Software, Series 1
  Access Restrictions
  This collection is stored off-site in commercial storage from which material is not routinely paged. Access to the collection will remain restricted until such time as the collection can be moved to Stanford-owned facilities. Any exemption from this rule requires the written permission of the Head of Special Collections.
  - Communication software, Subseries 1.1
    - ABT Microcomputer Software Data Trans: Microcomputer software for automatic telecommunications and data transfer for the Apple II+ and IIe by Mingche M. Li, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 114)
    - Access Software, Inc. Countdown, 1990, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 163)
    - Access Software, Inc. Mach 5, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. & computer cassetteCommodore 64/128 (Box 177)
    - Access Software, Inc. Mach 5, 1985, 1 computer cartridgeCommodore 64/128 (Box 177)
    - Activision, Inc. Postcards, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 54)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Backtalk 1.2, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 82)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Bulletin Board Construction Set, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 82)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Chameleon CRT Terminal Emulator, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 149)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Disk-Scanner (2 copies), 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 83)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Flash, 1986, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 74)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Floating Point Package/ Extended D.D.T., 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 149)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Kermit & Remote Control Accessory, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 75)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Quicktran - The Modem Accelerator, c. 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 76)
    - AT & T Enhanced TCP/IP Win3B LAN Interface Installation and Diagnostics Version 1.0, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 219)
    - AT & T TCP/IP Win/ 3B (5 disks), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 219)
    - AT & T TCP/IP Win/3B Applications Version 1.4 (5 disks), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 219)
    - Commodore Business Machines, Ltd. Modem Software, 1981, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 209)
    - Dow Jones & Co. Dow Jones Straight Talk, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Macintosh (Box 105)
    - Grafikon, Ltd. AnsiGraf, 1986, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 73)
    - Grolier Electronic Publishing, Inc. The Information Connection, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 47)
    - Haba Systems, Inc. HabaCom Communications Software, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 137)
    - Human Engineered Software, Inc. HesModem1, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeCommodore VIC-20 (Box 211)
    - Kuma Computers Ltd A-Ram, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 73)
    - Merit Software The Neverending Story II: The Arcade Game, 1991, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 163)
    - MichTron, Inc. Mi- Term, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 75)
    - MichTron, Inc. MichTron BBS, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 75)
    - Olduvai Software, Inc. Post Art, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 52)
    - Palantir Software inTouch Macintosh Communications, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 113)
    - Quantum Link Commodore presents Quantum Link telecommunications starter kit, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 196)
    - Sierra On-line Sierra OnLine, 1989, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 68)
    - Source Telecomputing Corporation Source Link Telecommunications Software, 1981, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 56)
    - Synapse Software, Inc. Mindwheel, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 167)
    - Thorn Emi Computer Software, Inc. Perfect Link, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 67)
    - U.S. Gold Dive Bomber, 1988, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 163)
    - United Software Industries Inc. ASCII Pro Telecommunications, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 60)
    - USA Today Sports Center Software ONline, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 163)
    - Weaver Consulting Southern California Business List (CD- List), 1992, 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.MS-DOS (Box 40)
  - Educational software, Subseries 1.2
    - Academy Software Typing Tutor and Word Invaders, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 150)
    - Advanced Ideas, Inc. LearningWare, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 32)
    - Adventure International Ghost Town, 1981, 1 computer cassetteTRS-80 (Box 214)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. A+ German, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 114)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. A+ Spanish, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 43)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. A+ Spanish, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 59)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. A+ Vocabulary, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 59)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Fun Learning: Biology Quiz (humans), 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 30)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Fun Learning: Life Science Quiz, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 64)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Fun Learning: Science Quiz (life), 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 30)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Fun Learning: U.S. Geography Quiz, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 30)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Fun Learning: U.S. Government Quiz, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 30)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Fun Learning: U.S. History Quiz, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 64)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Fun Learning: U.S. History Quiz (discovery to reconstruction), 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 30)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Fun Learning: Vocabulary Quiz, 1987, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 5)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Fun Learning: Vocabulary Quiz, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 30)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Fun Learning: World Geography Quiz, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 30)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Fun Learning: World History Quiz, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 64)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Fun Learning: World History Quiz (industrial revolution to today), 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 30)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Learn About Sounds in Reading, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 95)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Learn About Words in Reading 1, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 95)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Match Maker French Vocabulary Skills, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 86)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Reading Comprehension Skills 1, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 95)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Reading Comprehension Skills 3, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 34)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Science- grades 5 & 6 [Match maker Elementary Science facts], n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 35)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Spelling: grade 8, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 35)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. U. S. History, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 57)
    - American Training International, Inc. SuperCalc 3: Two Volume Edition, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 69)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. A-Calc, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 94)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Astrology by Harry Koons, 1985, 2 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 93)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Earth Views, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 149)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Enhanced Drawit!, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 149)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Genesis - the Stereo Molecular Modeler, 1986, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 74)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Halley Patrol (including Halley Watch), 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 149)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Human Design Disk, 1986, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 74)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Mapware, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 149)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Orbit- a trip to the moon, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 149)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Picture Plus/ Lister Plus (2 copies), 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 88)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Pokey Player, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 149)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Space Base, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 149)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. The Rhythm Composer, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 149)
    - Applied Optical Media Corporation World Vista, 1992, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.VIS (Box 23)
    - Arrakis Systems, Inc. Chemistry Volume 1: the atom (2 copies), 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 60)
    - Arrakis Systems, Inc. Chemistry Volume 2: the periodic table (2 copies), 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 61)
    - Arrakis Systems, Inc. Statistics Volume 1, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. MS-DOS (Box 69)
    - Artworx Software Company, Inc. Monkeymatch: It All Adds Up to Fun, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 95)
    - Atari, Inc. An Invitation to Programming 1: Fundamentals of Basic Programming, 1981, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 95)
    - Atari, Inc. An Invitation to Programming 2: Writing Programs One and Two, 1981, 2 computer cassetteAtari (Box 95)
    - Atari, Inc. An Invitation to Programming 2: Writing Programs One and Two, 1981, 2 computer cassetteAtari (Box 150)
    - Atari, Inc. An Invitation to Programming 3: Introduction to Sound and Graphics, 1981, 2 computer cassetteAtari (Box 95)
    - Atari, Inc. Atari 810 master diskette II / Beginning Sounds N-Z / Formatted Diskette II, n.d., 3 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 95)
    - Atari, Inc. Atari Speed Reading, n.d., 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 128)
    - Atari, Inc. Concentration, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 156)
    - Atari, Inc. Educational System Cassettes: Basic Electricity, 1979, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 84)
    - Atari, Inc. Educational System Cassettes: Basic Psychology, 1979, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 84)
    - Atari, Inc. Educational System Cassettes: Basic Sociology, 1979, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 84)
    - Atari, Inc. Educational System Cassettes: Business Communications (2 copies), 1979, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 84)
    - Atari, Inc. Educational System Cassettes: Counseling Procedures, 1979, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 84)
    - Atari, Inc. Educational System Cassettes: Principles of Accounting, 1979, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 84)
    - Atari, Inc. Educational System Cassettes: Principles of Economics, 1979, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 84)
    - Atari, Inc. Educational System Cassettes: U.S. Government, 1979, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 84)
    - Atari, Inc. Educational System Cassettes: U.S. History, 1979, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 84)
    - Atari, Inc. European Countries and Capitals, 1980, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 131)
    - Atari, Inc. Geography, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 85)
    - Atari, Inc. Juggles' House, 1982, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 132)
    - Atari, Inc. Juggles' Rainbow, 1982, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 132)
    - Atari, Inc. Math Gran Prix, 1982, computer cartridgeAtari (Box 72)
    - Atari, Inc. Memory Match, 1982, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 79)
    - Atari, Inc. Metric and Problem Solving: a amthematics program, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 87)
    - Atari, Inc. Music I: terms and notations, a music arts program, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 87)
    - Atari, Inc. Music II: rhythm and pitch, a music arts program, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 87)
    - Atari, Inc. Music III: scales and chords, a music arts program, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 87)
    - Atari, Inc. My First Alphabet, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 132)
    - Atari, Inc. Pre-Reading, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 88)
    - Atari, Inc. Prefixes, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 88)
    - Atari, Inc. Secret Formula Advanced, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 89)
    - Atari, Inc. Secret Formula Elementary, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 89)
    - Atari, Inc. Secret Formula Intermediate, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 89)
    - Atari, Inc. Spelling Bee, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 90)
    - Atari, Inc. Spelling in Context 7, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 90)
    - Atari, Inc. Spelling in Context 8, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 90)
    - Atari, Inc. States & Capitals, 1980, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 137)
    - Atari, Inc. Statistics I, 1980, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 132)
    - Atari, Inc. The Market Place: a social sciences simulation for Atari computers, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 86)
    - Atari, Inc. U.S. Geography high marc: a social sciences program for the Atari computer, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 91)
    - Atari, Inc. U.S. Geography high marc: a social sciences program for the Atari computer, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 91)
    - Atari, Inc. Word Games, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Avalon Hill Game Company ABC Caterpillar, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 20)
    - BCI Software, Inc. History and Geography, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 31)
    - BCI Software, Inc. Mathematics, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 32)
    - BCI Software, Inc. Plaque Man, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 190)
    - BCI Software, Inc. Pre-Schooler, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 200)
    - Behavioral Engineering Beginning Composition, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 43)
    - Behavioral Engineering Math Gallery, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 48)
    - Bertamax, Inc. Facts Match Series: Program for young learners, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 109)
    - Big Blue Disk Big Blue Disk Monthly Software Collection: Vol. 14, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 24)
    - BrainBank, Inc. Reading Comprehension 5: Practice D, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 55)
    - Broderbund Software, Inc. Calculus with Microsoft Windows Runtime, 1990, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. MS-DOS (Box 3)
    - Broderbund Software, Inc. Science Toolkit Master Module, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 55)
    - Broderbund Software, Inc. Science Toolkit Module 2: Earthquake Lab, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 55)
    - CBS Software Best Electronic Word Book Ever!, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - CBS Software Dinosaur Dig, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 199)
    - CBS Software Dr Seuss Fix-up the Mix-up puzzler, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 181)
    - CBS Software Math Mileage, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 181)
    - CBS Software Mr.Rogers' Neighborhood: Many Ways to Say I Love You, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 108)
    - CBS Software Mr Rogers' Neighborhood: Many Ways to Say I love You, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 181)
    - CBS Software Pathwords, 1984, computer cassetteDOS (Box 167)
    - CBS Software Pathwords, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 196)
    - CBS Software Wordfinder, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 118)
    - Children's Computer Workshop, Inc. Alpha Bean with Ernie, 1983, computer cartridgeAtari (Box 145)
    - Children's Computer Workshop, Inc. Hands On!, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. TRS-80 (Box 214)
    - Children's Television Workshop Cookie Monster's Letter Crunch, 1982, 1 computer cassetteTRS-80 (Box 215)
    - Children's Television Workshop Grover's Number Rover, 1983, 1 computer cassetteTRS-80 (Box 215)
    - Coleco Industries, Inc. Dr. Fix-up the Mix-up Puzzler, 1984, 1 computer cartridgeColecoVision & ADAM (Box 213)
    - Coleco Industries, Inc. Electronic Flashcard Maker, 1984, 1 computer cartridgeColecoVision & ADAM (Box 213)
    - Coleco Industries, Inc. ExperType, 1984, 1 computer cartridgeColecoVision & ADAM (Box 213)
    - Coleco Industries, Inc. Flash Facts: Fascinating Facts from American History, 1984, 1 computer cartridgeColecoVision & ADAM (Box 213)
    - College Edge Software Strunk and White Elements of Style.--Trivial Pursuit.--Typing Tudor 5.--StudyMate: The grade booster.--Right writer, 1991, computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 14)
    - Comm*Data Computer House, Inc. English Invaders Games, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 29)
    - Comm*Data Computer House, Inc. Gotcha Math Games, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 30)
    - Comm*Data Computer House, Inc. Math IQ educational program, n.d., 1 computer cassetteCommodore 64/128 (Box 177)
    - Comm*Data Computer House, Inc. Math Tutor, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 32)
    - Comm*Data Computer House, Inc. Primary Math Series, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 34)
    - Comm*Data Computer House, Inc. Toddler Tutor, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 37)
    - Commodore Business Machines, Ltd. A Bee C's, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeCommodore (Box 26)
    - Commodore Business Machines, Ltd. A Bee C's, n.d., 1 computer cartridgeCommodore (Box 203)
    - Commodore Business Machines, Ltd. English II, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 185)
    - Commodore Business Machines, Ltd. Geography, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 185)
    - Commodore Business Machines, Ltd. History, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 185)
    - Commodore Business Machines, Ltd. Number Nabber Shape Grabber, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 33)
    - Commodore Business Machines, Ltd. Number Nabber Shape Grabber, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 183)
    - Commodore Business Machines, Ltd. Speed/ Bingo Math, 1981, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 192)
    - Compton's New Media MultiMedia Audubon's Mammals, n.d., 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 158)
    - Computeach A B sCenes I, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 43)
    - Computeach ArithMAGIC: Counting, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple; IBM PC, DOS (Box 43)
    - Computeach ArithMAGIC: Subtraction, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple; IBM PC, DOS (Box 43)
    - CompuTeach Ruby the Scene Machine: Safari, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 116)
    - ComputerEasy International, Inc. Math Climbers, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 174)
    - ComputerEasy International, Inc. Spell Castle, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 69)
    - Computerose, Inc. Childpace (3 copies), 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. TRS-80 (Box 214)
    - Control Data Corporation Plato: Basic Number Facts, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 88)
    - Control Data Corporation Plato: Basic Number Facts Practice, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Texas Instruments 99/4(A) (Box 78)
    - Control Data Corporation Plato: Computer Literacy Introduction, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Texas Instruments 99/4(A) (Box 78)
    - Control Data Corporation Plato: Decimals, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 88)
    - Control Data Corporation Plato: Decimals Practice, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Texas Instruments 99/4(A) (Box 78)
    - Control Data Corporation Plato: Fractions Practice, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Texas Instruments 99/4(A) (Box 78)
    - Control Data Corporation Plato: Whole Numbers, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 88)
    - Creative Color Presents Creative Color presents Dinosaurs coloring book, 1993, computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 15)
    - Cross Educational Software Starfish: Computer Biology Lab, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 164)
    - Cyrstalvision Software Talking ABC's, 1993, DOS (Othertype 24)
    - DataBioTics Inc. Spot Shot, 1987, 1 computer cartridgeTexas Instruments 99/4(A) (Box 78)
    - Davidson & Associates, Inc. Math Blaster!, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 48)
    - Davidson & Associates, Inc. Math Blaster!, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 155)
    - Davidson & Associates, Inc. Speed Reader II: read, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 69)
    - Davidson & Associates, Inc. Spell It! Spell, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 90)
    - Davidson & Associates, Inc. Word Attack!, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 38)
    - Davidson & Associates, Inc. Word Attack Plus! French, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 4)
    - Davidson & Associates, Inc. Word Attack Plus! Spanish, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 4)
    - Deltron, Ltd. Planetarium: A complete observatory, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 76)
    - Design Ware European Nations and Locations, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 164)
    - Design Ware States & Traits, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 164)
    - Design Ware The Body Transparent, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 164)
    - Design Ware The Notable Phantom Version 1.01, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 118)
    - DesignWare, Inc. Body Transparent, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 21)
    - DesignWare, Inc. Creature Creator: do the monster match!, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 45)
    - DesignWare, Inc. European Nations & Locations, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 195)
    - DesignWare, Inc. Math Maze, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 32)
    - DesignWare, Inc. Math Maze: the amazing math game, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 86)
    - DesignWare, Inc. Mission: Algebra, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 124)
    - DesignWare, Inc. Mission: Algebra, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 148)
    - DesignWare, Inc. Remember! French Vocabulary Disk, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 55)
    - DesignWare, Inc. Remember! SAT Edition, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 55)
    - DesignWare, Inc. Remember! Spanish Vocabulary Disk, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 55)
    - DesignWare, Inc. Spellicopter, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 135)
    - DesignWare, Inc. States & Traits, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 195)